Perfect. Okay. Okay. So welcome, everyone, to the
What to Do With Your Sub call. Okay, so
I feel like we've got like some domination stuff already on the website, but this
one was a little bit more catered towards practical advice.
So things you can actually do on can with them.
And so yeah, hopefully you've learned some tips in here today.
Just let someone else in Sorry. Here we go.
So let's get started, Charlie. So the dynamic of the DOM and the sub domination
is not all about handing out harsh punishments and insults.
It's in fact about understanding your clients wants and needs active listening and
holding a safe space for your sub to fully surrender and let go of control.
When communicating with your sub, be clear, direct and confident, as this will show
them that you're an experienced dominatrix, and they could rest knowing they're in
the hands of a capable mistress. Always establish boundaries and the safe word that's
super important. And a
very important thing to note is to actually just ask questions and find out what
type of domination your sub is into. And this is totally fine.
It is okay to ask questions, I think. And, you know, people think that domination,
you've just got to tell them what to do and have all the answers, which in a way
that's true. But you only will have the answers by knowing by getting to know your
sub and knowing what they actually want, as I have so many different subs and what
one likes another one would really hate, and he would never come back to me again.
So it's always good to just find out exactly what they like before and before the
session. And then once you know what they like you can deliver to deliver them to
this as best you can. And only if that's in your comfort zone,
of course, there'll be some things that they ask you to do that you'll not be too
comfortable with. And it's okay not to do that.
And there's some things that I don't do because I'm not comfortable with that I used
to be but now I'm not anymore. And so yeah, so don't be afraid to say no and stick
to your boundaries as well while doing this.
And, but yeah, just touching on what I said a moment ago about holding a safe space
for your sub to fully surrender and let go of control.
A lot of your sub clients, a lot of them are going to be in really powerful successful
job roles. And usually with that comes a lot of stress as well.
And they're in these roles, and they're telling people what to do all day or they're
making the decisions. They've got all this weight on their shoulders, you know, so
this is why they enjoy this because it's a complete switch from what they're normally
used to. And this is where they can just put all of the power into somebody else's
hands and basically just be taken care of in that moment and don't have to, they
don't have to think in that moment. And so yeah, so a lot of your clients could be,
you know, doctors, lawyers like people like that.
And the next slide. Okay,
so what do we do with our subs who are new to submission.
Let's start by learning what to do with your subs, who are new to this world, and
want to give it a try. We want to introduce them by easing them in.
So you can try some of the different styles of domination listed below.
And because you'll get some guys that come in and they'll say, for example, a lot
of people come in and say, Oh, why don't want to ask me what I'm into first so I'll
just tell them I'm into domination. And then they'll go, Oh yeah, let's try that.
And they've never done it before. Or maybe they've only tried it once or twice and
not actually, you know, not done it properly.
So they'll, so then I could try something with them but then it'll be way too much
for them, because it's going to be something more on the more extreme ends.
So, if they're new and they just want to try it out.
It's always good to just start gentle because you'll probably scare so many people
off if you try some of the techniques. That we're going to talk about later on.
So a good one to start with, well, I always check that they want to try this first,
is JOI, which is jerk off instruction. So a lot of clients would enjoy
this, even if they're not into domination.
So it's good to start with. So you tell your sub exactly how to touch themselves
and if they're allowed to come. This can also be paired with edging
and CEI which is come eating instructions.
So maybe not a brand new person who's just started domination, unless he said he
likes to eat his own corn. So I wouldn't try that with a new person, unless they
actually said, but, you know, favour down the line, there's other subs that still
like JOI and CEI mixed together. So yeah, just know there's
always different things you can get involved when you're doing this.
So with JOI, you're basically, yeah, you're basically just telling them how to
rank themselves, basically. It's not to put it a better way.
And yeah, you can edge them as well. So with edging, you're basically bringing them
to the point of almost climaxing and then pulling it back, making them stop, and
then building it up again. And then before it happens, pulling it back.
And then if they're good and you feel like you want to that day, you can allow them
to come. And if not, you can tell them that they're not gonna come this time and
you'll do it next time or, you know, whenever you see fit.
But always bear in mind that you wanna keep your clients happy as well because you
want them coming back. So yeah, just try and gauge what they actually want and then
if they wanna come or not, or, you know, how long they wanna be edging for and stuff
like that, just gauge by their reactions and then go from there.
Okay, so another one you can try is foot worship.
So again, only do this with clients who are into feet and just always ask them
first if they're into this. So you can tease your client with your feet and use
oil if necessary or creams and stuff like that.
So basically you can just put your laptop a little bit further back or your camera,
whatever's on you and then just lift your feet up, like show them in the camera,
put them close, far away, show your soles, show the side of your feet.
Foot worship, I feel like it's just quite straightforward.
They literally just wanna look at your feet and worship them.
Sometimes you could maybe have a dildo and like, you know, you put your feet on the
dildo as if like you're wanking it, as if it's their dick kind of thing.
Some of them like that. And a lot of them ask you to use oils or creams instead just
to add something to it. But yeah, I think this one's quite straightforward.
But yeah, again, just make sure they're into this.
And by the way, if anyone has any questions throughout, please don't hesitate to
just unmute yourself and ask or write them down and ask at the end if you like or
anything to add at all. Okay, so body
worship. This is another one that most clients would enjoy even if they're not
into, you know, more harsher stuff of domination.
So you basically just allow your clients to worship your beautiful body from all
different angles. So some clients, they'll say they're into body worship
then they just wanna really just worship your bum or your boobs or your face.
So obviously your feet is a little bit a part of this.
And so yeah, another one that's quite straightforward and a lot of people would be
into and it wouldn't really scare them off if they wanna try domination.
And I know it doesn't really sound like domination because you know, it's not like
you're, they're just worshiping your body.
It's not anything too serious, but these are like the first levels of domination
and like the baby steps before you get into the more extreme stuff.
So yeah, this is one you can try with your clients.
There was a question there G, somebody, Gabriella asks, what kind of talk
would you do with foot worship? Oh yes, perfect, thank you.
I've just noticed that pop up. Okay, what kinds of talk would I do?
So this is something as well that I was gonna mention later on.
A lot of the time, if you, like your clients will.
Actually tell you what they want to hear.
They'll say, oh, am I just so worthless that, you know, like, I don't
know what, whatever it is that they've got in their heads, like they'll, they'll
just tell you, you know what I mean? Like, so with foot worship, what would I say
to them? I would just say things like, oh, you like these, these feet do you?
Would you like to touch them and kiss them and this and that?
Like, I just asked them, like, you know, that kind of stuff.
And sometimes, like I said, they like it to be a bit more sexual and talk about your
feet, like on them, like, you know, on their body parts and stuff like that.
But yeah, that's what I would say normally, just stuff like that.
I don't think, I'm sorry if that isn't really going into much detail there.
But this one, I feel like it is. Sometimes they ask for shoes, certain shoes,
don't they do? Like what they want you to wear, certain shoes, they might ask you
to, could you put these shoes on? Could you put these, like this shoe on or whatever
they want to look at your feet in shoes as well.
Yeah, definitely. Thank you for that. Yeah.
Sometimes they want you to wear heels or, or even stocking.
Converse. Converse I've had loads of times.
Can you wear a pair of Converse? Yep. I've never had that one, I love it.
So yeah, it's like I said, your client will normally tell you exactly what they want
and, you know, and then you could be like, Oh, you like how my feet look on these
converse and stuff like that, you know? So yeah.
A good one with these, like with the lesser, these things here that you've said is
like, like you said, Georgia, like, think about their context, like what they're
telling you. Cause a lot of the time they'll say things like, my wife's downstairs.
So I'll like work that into it. I'll be like, well, is your door shut?
Like, I want you to open the door a bit. Or if I'll be like, I'll tell them to worship
my body, but I can't hear you. Like you whispering, say it a bit louder, you know?
So there's like an element of risk. Yeah.
Like that don't know all the time. Yeah, they do.
They love that. Yeah. So
finally, this final one is
closed, clothed female, naked male. That's what it stands for.
So a lot of subs love this as well. Whether they're beginner or not.
And yeah, so basically they'll be naked while you'll be fully clothed.
And there's something about it that really makes them.
Yeah, it really makes them tick. And you can have them kneel below you while you're
naked and ask them how it makes them feel.
I like to ask this because they're kind of in a vulnerable position there.
Well, a bit more vulnerable as they're naked, they're below you and you're, you're
obviously fully dressed. I want to say below you, obviously you're both on different
sides of the screen, but you can kind of have your laptop.
So you're over them and then they're like below, you know what I mean?
And have them down. And again, asking how it makes them feel, depending
on what their response is. Then you can think, oh, where will
I take the rest of this conversation or the rest of this session?
Cause they might say, oh, I feel like a naughty little slut.
So then you can go straight into sissification because you know they're into that.
So yeah, so it depends on what they answer with and you can cater the rest of the
session to suit that. Okay, let's go to the next slide.
So now for the more experienced subs, humiliation.
So ask what type of humiliation he's into.
And if you're comfortable, deliver it to him.
You can do things like hand gestures to your client and have them perform humiliating
tasks. And you can also use insults. So when I say hand gestures,
I think one of the most popular ones is just the L sign.
So the loser sign, you can do that. And also like wanker, like, you know, do like
the wanker sign. You're silly saying some of these things on the course.
Don't feel silly on conversations with the clients, but on these sometimes they do.
But you can also make them do perform things and do things for you as well.
Humiliating things like dance, sing, you make them do certain positions.
I like to make mine twerk all the time. Don't know if I've got this sick little thing
in my head from watching, wanting to watch people twerk so often, but I always just
make them do it because they love it and it just makes me laugh.
And obviously it's humiliating for them and that's what they want.
They want to feel humiliated. But yeah, just always asking
what type of humiliation they're into as well.
So I'm just gonna let somebody else enter.
There we go. Because there's so many different types, so many different ways you
can take this. And like I said, what one person likes, another one might not.
So this is why it's always good to just establish first exactly what they're into.
And regarding the insults as well, obviously this is going to be catered for,
you know, each client is going to have different ones depending on what they're into.
And we actually do have a full list on the domination course of all
different insults as well in case you're not really sure what to say.
But this is actually one that I used to do more and I don't do as much anymore just
because I don't feel as good about this one anymore.
So I am a little bit less harsh with this, which is fine.
I don't feel like I've lost any clients because of it.
So yeah, just always stick to what feels good to you and don't do or say something
or, you know, if it doesn't feel good camming out of your mouth or, you know, when
you're typing it out or whatever else. So just, yeah, just always remain within your
own boundaries when practising domination as well.
Okay. So SPH, which stands for small penis humiliation.
I know it kind of falls under humiliation, but I wanted to do this one on its own
because this one is very, very popular in the domination world.
So just get to know it. If you're going to, you want to be practising domination,
then definitely get to know this one. Again, you can do hand gestures.
So you can do this as if you're wanking a small dick with your two fingers.
And this one as well, a lot of them like this one where you just put your little
pinky up as if that's, you know, you're measuring the same size as dick with this
and verbal insults. So you can say things
like, I bet you've never pleased a woman with that dick and you'll never will.
You'll never come name me with that. It's like, you know, stuff like that.
Baby dick, pin dick, just, I don't know, just anything, just like whatever.
Like to, you know, compare the dick to something small.
And also a lot of small penis humiliation clients love
getting off on the fact that you will tell all your friends about his tiny dick and
you will all laugh. So many of them always say, can you take a
picture or can you take a video? Or can you just tell your friends about this?
How many of them would there be? Would there be 10?
Would there be 20? Would they all just laugh at me?
And yeah, they have, it's crazy how all of them want this and all of them, but most
of small penis humiliation clients want you to sit with your friends and laugh about
it. So I just pretend to like, just write something on my phone and be like, oh,
just wrote in the WhatsApp group and told them about your tiny dick.
Haha, everybody's laughing at you. And you know, stuff like that.
I just do that. So yes, this is an interesting
one because sometimes as well, you'll open the cam and yeah, a lot of the time it
is small, but sometimes it's not even small.
It's actually quite big and you're like, what?
But you still just got to go with it because, you know, that's what they want.
You can't just dentate in mine and go, oh, it's actually quite big because that'll
kill their little fantasy in their heads that you've been creating.
So yes, so
sissification, I mentioned this one earlier.
This one is also quite popular, I think. And you can have your client dress up for
you and for them to do their makeup. And some clients even love the
idea that you're going to pimp him out to make money for you.
So not all of the sissification clients are into that, but some of them are.
So yeah, this one, you can have fun with it.
They'll tell you if they're into it, like I said, they'll call themselves a slut
or a whore or something like that. And they'll be like, you know, you're a naughty
little slut and stuff like that. Or sometimes you'll just turn the camera on and
they'll be fully dressed with a wig and makeup and lingerie and maybe put more effort
in than you that day. So, um, so yes, so you'll definitely know when
they're into this. Um, can I, can I buy in just,
um, they also like when they come on, they don't necessarily straight away be like,
Oh, I'm wearing this somewhere in that. They want you to like ask loads of questions
like, Oh, you're into that. So what are you wearing for me tonight?
And then like let them describe each item and then turn your cam on to see what they're
wearing and then massively compliment them.
And then I have a lot of pilots that ask them for tips for like, how should I do
my hair tomorrow? Or like, how should I wear my makeup?
Could you do like a makeup tutorial with me?
Could you show me your underwear? And then they'll get their underwear out.
Like I've got so many clients where we just like sit there and look at each other's
underwear and like, Oh wow, that's amazing.
Blah, blah, blah. Like, so it, it can be, it could be quite a lot, uh, just like
a feminine, you know, wanting advice from someone in a safe space that they can't,
they don't have other people to talk to in their life.
That makes sense. Sorry. Yeah, totally. Thank you for sharing, Sammy.
That's so true. They do just want advice all the time as well, don't they?
Reassurance that they look good, reassurance that this is okay.
And actually they've got someone who they can go, Oh my God, I love that top.
That looks amazing. Or that bra looks better with that.
Or those knickers look better with those shoes.
It can just be like that kind of, um, kind of relationship.
It doesn't, it doesn't always actually, you have to be anything other than that.
I have quite a few clients like that and it's, it's quite nice actually.
They're lovely. Yeah, I know it is nice. That's a good point, Sammy.
That's such a good point. Because sometimes we might think that they're busy clients
and they're acting like they are. It might not
be to just explore their identities. So, I always find that, um, guides like that
are normally, uh, weekday nights. Um, I can, once I do tell my cam on, cause obviously
after we've spoken for a little while and stuff, you know, you build that kind of
relationship where I think, yeah, okay, let's, let's come to cam.
And, um, it's normally guys that are, I can tell straight away in a hotel room, they're
probably corporate guys who do not have a safe space, do not have friends, whatever,
whatever in their life that doesn't allow them to be this person.
And this is like, they're just a little outlet of, I don't even know what the word
is, but you know, like it, it's actually quite refreshing.
And it's actually really nice. Some of these calls, I really enjoy them.
Yeah. I mean, they could be trans women. They could be trans women, but that's not
always the case, but some guys will be at home and they will literally get their
whole wardrobe out. And I love that cause I'm like, Oh my God, let me show you mine.
Hang on, hang on. You can have real good fun with those calls.
Um, yeah. And it's just, it's just like a little safe space for them to just have
a chat with you, you know, like as if it was a girlfriend bringing you, um, and saying,
Oh, what shall I wear tonight? You know, like, yeah, that's lovely.
Yeah. So yeah, something to share that with you.
Yeah. Thank you for sharing and girls. Yeah.
A hundred percent. It's so nice, isn't it?
When it's like that, because you are allowing them to just explore this part of themselves,
like you said, who they can't do this, you know, in their normal lives.
So, um, in the day to day life. So yeah. So we're allowing them to do that.
Um, and it's fun as well. It's fun for them.
It's fun for us. So, um, I'll give advice.
I'm like, no, I don't like that skirt with that top.
This one looks better. Show me this one on, you know, like I'm, I'm quite honest
with it as well. I'm like, nope, these shoes look better with this.
Like that's when it comes to this call, they, they don't want you to just be like,
Oh yeah, you look amazing in everything. Like, be honest, tell them like, no, these,
these boots look better with this, but that's what they're camming on for the authenticity
of it as well. Exactly. Exactly. Amazing.
Thank you girls. But, um, but yeah, like there's that side to it, but then also,
like I said, some of them, like the idea, you're going to pimp them out and make
money off them, not all of them like this.
They'll tell you if they like this. Um, so yeah, so just when you're getting to
know a new sub, obviously once you, once you've got to know each other over some
time, then, you know, you can maybe try and explore different things and stuff like
that. But in the beginning, especially you just really want to idea of what they
like, um, because you don't want to say something that's going to scare them off.
Um, because just your subs can be your loyal, most loyal clients, if you get the
dynamic right and the relationship right.
And if you really listen to what they want, um, so yeah, so saying to someone, Oh
yeah, I'm going to pimp you out so you can make some money for me.
And they don't like that. They would, they would really probably just run off.
Never come back. But whether some clients, they love that, and they'd love to hear
you talk about that. And the fact that they're going to get all dressed up, do the
hair nice and go and stand on the corner of the street and, you know, wait for the
guy to come past or anyone to come past or whatever.
And so yeah, that's another, another thing you can talk about with them.
And the great thing about cities as well that they will always tell you, like, there's
no like guessing with them, you know, like some guys come on, and then you're like,
Oh, I like everything. But they will be quite specific and be like, I think they're,
in my, you know, in my experience, they've always been more expressive clients that
will kind of give you straight away what they like, what they don't, what their
boundaries are. I don't know, I find them quite very refreshing clients for me.
Yeah, no, definitely. They are, they are very, they say exactly what they want and
how they want to kind of thing, like you said, And even when they, when they are
clients who are like, Oh, yeah, I want you to like, pimp me out with other men, stuff
like that. They'd be like, Oh, I always say stuff like, what men do you like, I like
this type of man. And then they'll really get into that of like, what, what they're
looking for and what they, what they want you to make them do, if that makes sense.
Yeah, yeah, exactly. And then that's a whole other like, 10, 20, who knows, 30,
40 minutes of the conversation to go into that.
Yeah, I love, I love these clients. To me, they're my, I just love it.
Oh, that's nice. Okay. Okay,
so the last one on here is CP, which is corporal punishment.
So this is basically just having your client hit
themselves, basically, or spank themselves and stuff like that.
So you can start off slow and gentle and see how your sub responds and go from there
and only have your clients spank areas of the body that are safe.
So just like large, fleshy areas, you don't want them hitting the back by where the
kidneys are and stuff like that. The bum is always a very safe option and the thighs
as well, quite safe. So yeah, just bear that in mind.
And you'll get some clients that are quite experienced in this and
the certain techniques that you can use with them.
But only if they really know how to do it themselves, there's like a way of how they
hit themselves in the same spot over and over and over time, that spot will start
to go a little bit numb, will lose feeling.
So then you can carry on the session for longer.
But yeah, stuff like that, you want to make sure your clients is actually, they're
actually experienced in this phase because you don't want them just hitting themselves
over and over and over and over and over and over if it's going to cause some bad
damage. That's just me. If they want it, then some
people would give it regardless of what it's going to do to them.
Whereas I obviously want to give my clients the best possible experience, but I also
I'm thinking about after the session as well.
I don't want to leave them really, really damaged from the session with me.
So yes, but usually with corporate punishment, usually it's just like the odd spank
here or there, or if you need to punish them, you can have them give themselves a
spank or something like that. Doesn't need to be anything too serious.
But like I said, you will get the clients in who are really into this and they want
to show you how long they can do it to themselves for basically.
I think it's good to mention there as well, that a lot of guys do go to that level
with corporate punishment because they want to be needless.
They don't want to be needy. That can be one of their biggest triggers or traumas,
being needy or having needs. So having absolutely no needs and even to the point
where they think that people are laughing at them and they're literally being humiliated
and doing things they would never do can be a trauma relief thing, which is why it's
so important to hold a boundary for them and to make sure that they are safe because
we are the ethical community and we do want to be practising ethically and holding
a safe space for them. So whatever you think is best there, some people will go way
beyond what they want to because it's an antidote to their trauma, but it's
not necessarily the best thing for them. And
stuff like that. So, so yeah, so just always just be aware and just think, is this
going a little bit too far now? And you don't have to, you know, you don't have to
necessarily say that to them. You can always just take the conversation in a different
direction, like take the session somewhere else.
Remember, you're the Dom here, so you can always take it down a different avenue
or pull it back or whatever else if it's going too far.
Because we do want to look after them at the end of the day.
Like I said at the very beginning, and it's not, domination is not about just being
harsh and, you know, punishments and insults and stuff like that.
It's actually so much more. Yeah. Okay
then, so now we'll move on to how to handle the expert level subs.
So some subs have been explored in the side of themselves for decades and like the
more extreme side of domination. Again, before trying any of the techniques listed
below, make sure your client's actually into this as if not, it could scare them
off. I know I've mentioned this a few times, but yeah, I think it's just a
key, you know, a key point with domination, just always asking questions
in the start and finding out exactly what they want.
Okay, so FinDom or financial domination as it's known, is
a good one to use on cam. I absolutely love this one.
And basically it's where your subs, they
want to hand over their money to their mistress and you basically, you deserve their
money more than they do. That's how they like to feel.
And they're basically your pay pig or human ATM.
These are some words you can use with them.
You can call them piggy, stuff like that.
Then they know what that means. It just means pay pig.
And you can ask your sub to send you tips.
And in extreme cases, you'll be in full control of their finances, taking most of
it for yourself and giving them an allowance to live on.
So I actually had a guy once, well, it was my client, like he'd come back but like
he was just one guy, just one client on this.
So this is not very, you know, it doesn't happen all the time, but it does happen.
He had me download this thing called team viewer and I could view his laptop as well,
as well as mine. And he wanted me to go onto his laptop and transfer his money from
his bank out into my bank. And looking back now, I think to myself, I don't know
if I would do that these days, but yet it was crazy.
They just wanted to take all the money out and just leave them like a hundred pounds
or whatever left. It wasn't that much in there, to be honest.
It wasn't like it was like, you know, thousands of thousands, but still, like they
like the idea of you taking all their money as they're not worthy of it and they
don't deserve it. You deserve it all. A lot of the time as well, they've also said
things like, do you have a boyfriend and stuff like that?
And they say, I wanna send you money to use on your boyfriend to take him out and
stuff like that. I got that a lot as well.
I mean, they're not all gonna be into that, but a lot of them, like the fact that
you're spending their money on somebody else and especially your partner.
So much to know about findom and we actually have a lot more information on this,
on the course, on the website. But yeah, this is a really good one.
If you've got a subset into this, this is so good for you because of course, you're
making more money off the same, you know, you're making more money from these guys.
So yeah, I love this one. Can I just
add one little thing in? Of course. I just wanted to say as
well, I think like, I don't know if there's many new girls in the call, but like
a lot of new girls, they watch like media and TikTok and stuff like that.
And they think it's, you know, there's like documentaries and stuff where they think,
oh, it's really easy to get like a pay pig.
And I think, yeah, you definitely can get a pay pig.
Like in my experience, a hundred percent, yes you can.
But like, you have to, I've made like a long, like a year's worth of relationship
with someone before I got to that stage. And I just think that's really important
to remember that, like, they don't just come along and be like, oh, here's my wallet,
have everything. Like, I feel like they want to get to know you, like on a personal
level, you chat for like a long time first and then you get to that stage, if that
makes sense. Like, I don't know. I feel like there's sometimes there's a little bit
of false advertising. Like there's always the odd one.
That is going to be like that, but I think the more you put time and effort into
a client, then they potentially do become like this.
That makes sense. Yeah. 100%. Sammy, thank you for mentioning that.
Yeah. And I think with the, yeah, like you said, with the things that are in the
media and then all of the new cam document, I always, I watched documentaries and
I think, well, that's a little bit of false belief, you know, like, yeah, people
are going to join think, oh, I can just turn my computer on and get around like a
thousand pounds in five minutes. Yeah. Doesn't always like it, but after like a while
of really like, you know, spending time with that person, chatting to them, getting
to know them, then, then, yeah. But I don't know.
I think there's a process that you have to go through.
And I think like the whole point of our company is to be authentic and, and just
explain that you do get some of the guys like that, but they're like one in a million
in my, in my, in my opinion, like in my experience.
Yeah, definitely. Of course. Like, and yeah, these documentaries and stuff have made
it a little bit harder. Well, not harder, but made it a little bit more unrealistic
because like you said, maybe people are going to think that they can just log on
and get a pay pick straight away, which is not the case.
Um, yeah, they definitely, you got you a hundred percent can, if you then put like
the consistency and the time and keep on spending that time with that client log
in when they want, like, you know, when they, when you know, they're free, you know,
that they're going to be free tomorrow night and nine o'clock log in at nine o'clock,
be there, like chat to them. And then after like a certain amount of time, you can
definitely do that, but you have to put, you know, like the, the,
the work in, I suppose is the word, I don't know, you know, like the, the timing
and the effort with them, and then they're going to spend with you as much as, you
know, you want, but I don't think it's as easy as just logging in and being like,
Oh yeah, give me your money. Yeah, no, definitely not proper, like subs
who are really into this, they'll detect straight away that you're not an experienced
dominatrix because an experienced dominatrix would not do that.
They would know that they need to build a relationship first.
So you kind of like shooting yourself in the foot, really, if you just try and be
greedy in the beginning, because they're going to be like, Oh no, this is not normally
how it works. Like, and then they'll leave and find an experienced dominatrix who's
going to actually, you know, do it all properly.
So yeah, always building up the relationship with your clients first, um, but they
are out there and you can definitely find them just, um, a million percent.
They're definitely out there, but some guys will come in and they'll be like, Oh,
I want to give you all my money. And like, the thing I'll say is, I won't say, Oh
yeah, tip me or whatever. I'm like, okay, let me, let me find out some stuff about
you first. Like what, like, tell me some stuff about you.
Tell me five things about you that are really interesting.
And then you like hook them, if you know what I mean?
Yeah, definitely. Perfect. Thank you for your input, Sammy.
No worries. We'll head into the next one.
Okay. So blackmail. Some subs like to fantasise about this and not give any
real information to blackmail with. Whereas some subs will actually give you their
wives contact details at this many times.
Um, and I knew that it's been true because they've sent me their Facebooks and stuff
like that. And I've seen the guy that I've seen on the cam, like in the photo with
her on like the profile picture and stuff like that.
So they actually will give you the full contact sometimes.
Um, I would say to tread lightly with this one and never actually expose them.
So of course they like the fantasy of the blackmail, like, you know, you're going
to potentially expose them if they don't do as you say, or, you know, whatever it
is, whatever's going on in that session, but never actually do it, even if they don't
do as they say or whatever it is, like never actually do it.
But it's just one, it's more of a fantasy, this one.
So using their wives names a lot. So for example, like, oh, how would Sarah
feel if she knew you were on here chatting to me while she's in bed and just dropping
the name in a lot and asking, you know, how do you think you would feel about this?
What would she do? Would she, you know, would she break up with you?
Like, you know, how would she react? Stuff like that.
They really like to talk about how, what might happen if, if they were to find out
whoever it is that they want to be blackmailed with.
Um, so yeah, so you want to make them believe that, you know, you, you actually
blackmail them and, you know, you're going to help them, but never actually do it.
Um, and again, this is one just at your, do at your own, you know, what feels good
to you. Um, but usually this is just a fantasy for them.
And, um, It never has to be taken too far.
Someone just came up in the chat. Okay,
so if you don't do, if they don't do what you say, how do you punish them after you've
been, okay, let's see. How do I
punish them if they're not doing as I say?
I mean, they usually would be doing as you say, but if not, what
would I do? Feel like I'd just be like, are you even that serious?
Like, are you even into this? Like, what's the point of all this?
You know what I mean? And I'd just be like, I don't know, cause I feel like it doesn't
really happen often. So I don't know what I would do.
Cause if it ever happens, does that ever happen with you, Sammy?
Like you're telling them, like you're telling them what to do.
I think if they want you to punish them because they know they're not going to complete
a task, they'll kind of hint about that before.
You know what I mean? So if they're, they will normally say like something like,
oh, what will you do if I don't do this? And then you tell them to do something and
then they don't do it. Cause they've already pointed that like, I want you to punish
me. Yeah, they will. They usually even tell you how to punish them, don't they?
Yeah. They don't give you all the information.
Yeah, so if they said that just out of the blue and you weren’t sure because
they just not completed it and they were like, you know, I need to punish you now.
And they said, oh, how are you going to punish me?
I would just probably say, well, what would be the worst way I could punish you?
And then go from there and let them lead with the conversation maybe.
That's what, that's probably what I would do.
Or how does it feel to disappoint me? And is your wife as disappointed as I am?
Is that, is that something? Oh, that's amazing.
Yeah. Make them, basically that's what they want, don't they?
Yeah. Exactly. Yeah, they will tell you what they want, honestly.
Just, just listening, just actively listening.
But they will just, they will tell you. Like, yeah, it's good to know about the different,
you know, it's good to know about all of this stuff and have ideas of what to do
with them. But like I said earlier, every single session is going to be so different
because every single client's got their own desires, their own fantasies, you know,
their own things they want to explore. So yeah, usually.
And you could even say, you know, if they're giving you nothing, you could even say,
like you said, like, are you wasting my time?
Because I've literally just got 17 emails where I've been doing this call of other
guys that are going to literally, that want me right now.
So can we clarify if you're wasting my time or not?
But like, do it in like a, a bit of a strict, but a bit of a sexy way.
Like, I have other guys waiting for me, like, what are you doing?
Yeah. And guys, they always like the fact that you're desirable.
Yeah. If they're giving you nothing, then that's what I would do.
Okay. I hope that answers your question. Thank you.
Okay. So moving on to CBT, which in this world means cock and ball
torture. You can have your sub tie their cock and balls up with string, make
him hit himself with a wooden spoon or something similar.
And sounding can also be used with this, but only do this with subs who explored
this before. So for anyone who doesn't know, sounding is where it's
usually a metal rod. They will stick right down in the hole of their penis.
So I would only do this with them if like they said they wanted to do it.
I'd just be like, have you done this before?
You experienced in this? Because I think this one could go terribly wrong if they
don't know what they're doing. I can't even imagine how that must feel by the way.
But yeah, some of them love it. And sometimes you'll just open the cam and they've
already like got the hole, like dick and balls tied up with string.
And it looks like it's, you know, looking bulging and looking like there's, I don't
know, it doesn't look great, but yeah, they love it.
But I would just, again, be quite careful and always remember use of a safe word
because yeah, you don't want them to feel like they're just, you know, they can go
further and further to please you or to not say no.
And then, you know, next thing you know, they're left with loss and damage.
So yeah, that's just be careful with that one.
And this can also kind of be paired with chastity I'd say.
So chastity is basically where, well, it's actually a little bit different, but sometimes
the ones who are into this, like they'll then throw a cage on afterwards.
So it's where they put a cage. On their dick.
So this is actually, like I said, it's a little bit different, and maybe clients
who are into chastity are not gonna be into cock and ball torture.
But I'll chat a little bit about chastity anyway, as it is a part of domination.
So yeah, with chastity they're put on their dick, and sometimes they're dicking balls
in a cage, so they obviously can't pleasure themselves properly with it on.
Well, they can't really pleasure themselves at all.
And it's all about just like, you know, you being the ownership
of what they can do to themselves. So you can tell them, you know, I want you to
keep it on, keep the cage on all day while you're at work.
Sometimes they will even have keys and they'll want to send the keys to you.
I've had many guys over the years tell me that the key is on the way, they're posting
the key, like the key that opens the cage.
But I've never actually been sent one. But people definitely do send them out and
know that people will be sending them out, but I've never had one.
But yeah, so sometimes like they will actually want to give you the key, so then
they cannot open it at all until you send the key back to them.
So yeah, like I said, that's a bit different to cock and ball torture, but sometimes
they go together. So finally, okay,
so the last one is a slave. So some subs will
want to be your full time or part time slave.
And you can even have them sign a contract to say they're owned by you.
So you can find contracts online, or you can just write up your own contract.
Doesn't need to be, you know, loads and loads of detail.
It can just be like 10 points of how they're going to obey you.
And then you can have them write this out.
Like sometimes I even have them write it out, like, and on a bit of paper, they'll
write out all of my rules. And then they'll sign it and stuff like that, and send
me a photo that they've done it. Or like show me on the cam or whatever.
And also, yeah, so like I wrote there, have them write out your rules daily and perform
tasks for you. So having a, oh, sorry, there we go.
Having a dedicated slave is as much of a job for the Dom as it is the sub.
So yeah, so this one, it's a little bit more than just what you're doing in the cam
sessions, because you can have them do things outside of the session.
So they're always, you know, thinking of you and obeying you and stuff like that.
So with these clients, this is more for ones that you've built a good relationship
with, and you know, it's more than just a one-off client, that's for sure.
I have some rules here. I was going to read out for my last slave that I had him
write out every day and he would send me a photo every day.
I have him writing out the rules. Okay. So this is just an example of some rules
you can set your slaves. I will obey, serve, and do my absolute best to please
Goddess Ruby. That's my name. Obviously you would just use whatever name.
I worship Goddess Ruby and her body. So this one was really into like, you know, worshiping
my body. So I worked this into the rules.
So, you know, whatever they're into, just change up your, your slave rules for them.
And then they're going to love that because it's all the things that they're after.
It says it in the contract anyway. So yeah.
So I must ask permission from Goddess Ruby to satisfy any of my needs.
I am the property of my owner, Goddess Ruby.
I will not waste Goddess Ruby time. This one was a bit of a time waster, so I was
like, I'm going to add that in there because I don't want to waste me time anymore.
I will not be passive in saving Goddess Ruby.
The needs of my owner will always come before the needs of my own.
My place is on my knees below my owner, Goddess Ruby.
And finally, I'm grateful to have the opportunity to save Goddess Ruby and I will
not take it for granted. So you can take some inspiration from that and also look
online as well. There's loads of different contracts you can write up for them.
But obviously that's just one part of it.
So talking about the tasks for them to do outside of, outside of cam,
you can have them do tasks for you that like, it's basically like stuff for themselves.
So when you're at work today, I want you to go into the toilet and, you know, look
at, look at the photo of me on my profile and like, you know, pleasure.
Yourself, or I don't know, like whatever it is that they like, or like, you know,
maybe they're not into that, maybe they're into cock and ball torture.
I want you to go into the toilet while you're at work today and like slap your balls
a few times thinking about me, or I don't know, you know, like whatever it is they're
into, make up something that you want them to do outside of your session, and then
ask them about it on your next session. This kind of keeps like, this keeps them
hooked and this keeps them coming back to you because, you know, it's not like they
leave the session and then they don't think about you anymore.
They have to think about you again if you're setting them tasks to do.
I've got a little bit more to say about this, but I'll say a little bit later on
in the call. I've just noticed something in the chat, one second.
Surely don't give out your real address to send the key to you.
No, so you can actually, you can actually have it sent over places.
So like, you can have it just sent, you know, to like a pickup location kind of thing,
like everywhere has places like that. Like I said, I've never actually been sent
one, so I've never given my address for it, but if I was to do it, I would send it,
have it sent to a pickup location, like somewhere you can just get it sent to and
you go pick it up yourself. So yeah, yeah, never give out your real address.
Let's move on. Okay.
Customise to their fantasies. Love
this photo from one of our shoots. Some of
your subs will have very specific fantasies.
Sometimes, even if, sometimes an event has happened in their life, which has shaped
their sexual fantasies. Ask your sub to fully explain the fantasy and then it basically
becomes a role play. These
clients can be your loyal clients as you're getting to know them on a deeper personal
level. They're opening themselves to you and putting their trust in you to allow
them to explore this fantasy. So like I said, there is all these different areas
of domination, but also a lot of the time, there's just very specific, I
can't even say the words, I've just said it, very like, you know, specific things
that they want to explore that you'll have never heard of.
So for example, I have this one guy that I've had for years that wants me to wear
ankle socks, mishmash ankle socks, so not the same, you know, not the same colour,
and then just pretend to kick him in the balls.
So I just like kick the air and just pretend I'm kicking him.
And he loves that. And he actually told me that something happened in his childhood.
Like I won't go into the story, but some similar, similar thing happened
and this is why like, he has this fantasy now.
So like I said, he's been coming back for years and years and years.
He's so loyal because I know his very personal fantasy and I allow
him to explore that and we explore it together.
So yeah, so these can be very loyal clients, which is good.
Okay, so Elge just wrote, these are my favourite clients, can chat for hours with
them after a session and you don't have to do much work as you know exactly what
they want. So yeah, this is perfect. Yeah, they'll tell you what you want and
then you can just speak about it and speak about it in detail and, you know, really
just get into it and keep the conversation going as long as possible, of course.
Okay, so writing down notes about these clients is vital as remembering small details
is what counts and your subs will love you for it.
So yeah, I think that one's pretty straightforward.
Can't really give much practical advice on this one because like I said, like one
guy wants me kicking him, pretending to kick him in the balls with different coloured
ankle socks on whereas another, he wanted me to use a deodorant bottle on myself,
which I actually couldn't. There's no way I could do that, but that's because of
something that his fantasy that it's something that happened when he was younger,
a girl with a deodorant bottle and this and that.
So yeah, obviously they're both completely different.
So yes, just writing down notes and remembering small details for each client.
You don't want to get them mixed up. You know, you don't want someone to come in
and think, oh yeah, I remember he liked this and then it just wasn't what his personal
fantasy was. And you know, they've been vulnerable enough to tell you this.
So remembering or just writing it down is it.
I'm gonna really go a long way for you. And
finally, it's all about connection. Your relationships
with your subs is carried out online. So building a strong connection is important
as you want them to come back time and time again.
If you genuinely enjoy this, it will be easier to build a connection with your subs.
Oh, I don't know where I was going with that.
Sorry, think of them as, and then I didn't write anything else.
Sorry, I don't know, I didn't finish that, but there, I don't know where I was going
with that. Keep in contact with your subs in between sessions and ask
them to perform tasks for you outside of your session will keep them thinking of
you. Tasks can be anything from wearing panties to work or performance sub poses
while reciting your rules, be creative. So again, depending on what your
sub is into, you will think of a task for them that caters
to that. And while dealing with slaves, you are training
them to be the very best slave for their mistress, but you're also helping them be
a better person. So you can ask your slave what they need to change to improve
the quality of their life and have them do this under your watchful eye.
So this is a part of domination that I actually really like because obviously a lot
of the time you are just, you know, humiliating them or having them hit themselves
or, you know, doing like harsh things to them.
So I like this aspect of domination as well and this is something that probably isn't
spoken about enough. So this is, like I said, this is more for slaves, like full
-time subs. So you can ask them, you know, what do you need
to change in your life to improve it? Maybe they wanna lose some weight or save some
money or I don't know, whatever it is, they're normally quite common ones.
But a lot of the time they'll just say, you know, like a lot of time it is that they
wanna lose weight or whatever, it could be anything, but let's just say lose weight,
for example, because this is normally what a lot of my subs have said to me.
So then I'll say, yeah, okay, cause I want you to be in a bit of better shape for
me so when I'm, you know, when I'm looking at you, I've got something good to look
at or you've got a nice, healthy, strong body so you can save me for longer or whatever,
like turn it back to you, like that they're doing this to save you, but obviously
it's not, they've told you that they wanna do that for themselves, they wanna lose
this weight. So you can say to them, okay, so for the next two
weeks or however long, you know, however long you've got your arrangement going for,
I want you to check in every single time or maybe not ever, it depends on how serious
they are, maybe they can check in every day, maybe they've only, you know, they can
only do it every few days, whatever it is, just, you know, it's gonna be different
for everyone. Well, I want you to check in with all your meals and your weight and
photos, before and afters, stuff like that.
So yeah, so this is like, this is a good one because you're actually helping them
improve something that they need to improve and maybe as you're, you know, you're
on them and like to do this, maybe they will actually do it, maybe this is what they
need, like this is the push they need to actually change this past themselves and
so yeah, I like doing this because like I said, it feels good to me to help them
like improve as well as, you know, doing all the harsh stuff or whatever while we're
in the fantasy of it and I just wanted
to read as well, I have some questions here, I've read these before, so
some of the clients, like I said, they'll wanna be slaves and it is like a full-time
job for you and them, well, maybe not a full-time job for you, but it is a lot of
work, so clients like this, it's more for the really serious ones and if you have
a proper arrangement going on, then they're coming to you to chat with you, you know,
a certain amount of times a week and you know that you're making a certain amount
of money out of them, so doing this little bit of extra work, it's not really
extra work as in like you're getting paid back for the kinds of thing so I wouldn't
just send out this list of questions to any clients because I wouldn't go into all
this work for nothing, like I said, it would be with someone who's actually coming
back regularly and you know, spending money regularly, okay.
So this is what I sent to them, below I have a list of questions for you to answer,
answer in as much detail as possible as I wanna get to know as much as possible about
your fantasies and desires, I've read these up.
For but I think you girls haven't heard them yet.
What do you enjoy most about the dom sub relationship?
Describe your perfect dom. What makes you go completely weak?
Regarding humiliation and insults, how harsh do you like it?
Are you into chastity? Are you into SPH? Are you into sissification?
Are you into cuckold? Are you into cock and ball torture?
Are you into anal play? What are your limits?
How much time do you have to devote to me?
What are your fantasies? Tell me something you've not told anybody else.
How do you plan to please me? What do you want from me?
What might I find you useful for? What services can you provide for me?
Do you have any specialised skills that may be of use to me?
Do you have any fetishes? And finally, is there anything else you want to tell me?
So I send these out to my full-time slaves because then, I mean, you can,
you know, write whatever you want but I feel like in these questions it covers mostly
everything so I can get a really good idea of what they actually want and then
you'll have so much, so much to do with them because if they're answering all these
questions in detail, which they should be as you've asked them to in the beginning,
you can just flip back through the questions if you're stuck in session and then
be like, oh yeah, I remember he said he was into cuckold or he was, he wants to try
anal play or whatever and then you can try that in your sessions with him.
So yes, I think that brings us to the end.
Does anybody have any questions or would anyone like to share?
Anything? Nope.
Let me just check the chat. There
we go. Okay then, so I don't think there's any questions today but obviously
you all have my number and you can all contact me whenever you like.
Just ask any questions about Domination or anything in general really but yes, I
hope you girls enjoyed and I hope you've learned something new today but yeah, if
you use anything that we spoke about today on the call and it goes well with your
subs, please let us know how it goes and yeah, just final bit of advice, safe
word, super important. Taking it, building it up slow with new subs, you know,
really finding out what they like before you go or going blazing with it all and
yeah, just staying true to yourself and your own boundaries as well as your subs
but yes, thank you for coming today girlies and we'll see you on the
next one. I think the next one, let's just double check on the next callers.
Okay, so we have the welcome call next Monday so I don't think we'll see any views
on that one but next Tuesday at 9pm, Tuesday the 12th,
we have the getting back to business call which is basically just all about getting
back on track after summer, after the kids are back in school, stuff like that, just
you know, getting back into a good routine after camp.
So yeah, hopefully we'll see you there next week at 9pm on Tuesday but yeah,
enjoy your evening girls and I'll see you soon.
Thank you, G! No worries, dear, thank you for your impossible ladies.
See you later!